mynaturalmarket.com 2016-10-27

# Natural, Organic Vitamins & Supplements | MyNaturalMarket.com

|  | 

|   
---  
  
## Privacy Notice

The Site is owned by WFM Online operating as MyNaturalMarket. At MyNaturalMarket, we want to make your experience online satisfying and transparent. This Privacy Policy describes how we collect and use your information. Because we gather certain types of information about our users, we feel you should fully understand our Policy and the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This Privacy Policy discloses what information we gather and how we use it.

By accessing or using our Site via a computer, mobile phone, table, console or other device, you consent to our Privacy Policy. We may modify this Privacy Policy at any time and those modifications will be effective upon posting. Your continued use of our Site constitutes your acceptance to our Privacy Policy and any updates. This Privacy Policy is a part of, and is subject to, our Terms of Use.

INFORMATION MyNaturalMarket GATHERS AND TRACKS

MyNaturalMarket gathers the following types of information about users: Information that users provide through optional, voluntary submissions or through permissions. Often these are provided to receive our electronic newsletters, to participate in our message boards or forums, to email a friend, by using the Site and from participation in polls and surveys. This information may include Personal Information such as your name, image, birth date, email and physical address, telephone number, gender, contact lists, social media information and profile, geolocation information, interests, and, when needed, credit card information.

Information MyNaturalMarket gathers through aggregated tracking information is derived mainly by tallying page views throughout the Site but also through other interactions you may have throughout and with the Site. Types of this information include your telephone number, device identifier and hardware information, IP address, browser type and language, cookie information, system type, whether you have enabling software to access certain features, access times, referring website URLs, information about your purchases and other information about your interactions with us.

This information allows us to better tailor our content to readers needs and to help our advertisers and sponsors better understand the demographics of our audience.

We may combine information with that which you provide to us via other means, such as by the telephone. We may also combine information with data that is publically available or with data from third parties.

CHILDREN'S PRIVACY - We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from children under 13.

PROCESSES MyNaturalMarket USES TO GATHER INFORMATION

We automatically collect information within our products and services or stored by your browser or device. We use a variety of methods to collect this information, including, but not limited to, cookies and pixel tags/web beacons ("Collection Tools"). We may place a text file called a "cookie" in the browser files of your computer. The cookie itself does not contain Personal Information although it will enable us to relate your use of the Site with information that you have provided. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. MyNaturalMarket uses cookies to track user traffic patterns (as described above). Our advertising system delivers a one-time cookie to better track ad impressions and click rates.

You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. If you've set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you will receive the warning message with each cookie. You do not need to have cookies turned on to use the Site. However, you do need cookies to participate actively in message boards, forums, polling and surveys. Also, you may not have access to many features that make your experience more efficient and some of our services and features may not function properly. You can still place product orders over the telephone by contacting our customer service number at 1 (866) 646-8098. Note that our Site may not recognize or respond to Do Not Track (DNT).

USE OF INFORMATION

We offer a free electronic newsletter to users. MyNaturalMarket gathers the email addresses of users who voluntarily subscribe. Users may remove themselves from this mailing list by following the link provided in every newsletter that points users to the subscription management page. Users can also subscribe to the newsletters at the time of registration.

MyNaturalMarket uses information to enhance our user's experience on the Site, whether to provide interactive or personalized elements or to better prepare future content based on the interests of our users. We use information to improve our communications, including administrative messages and other communications, with you and other customers. We use information to communicate with you about your account, your orders or your experiences with MyNaturalMarket. We use information to inform you about our products, services, and events, and for other promotional purposes. MyNaturalMarket uses information to administer contests, promotions, events, surveys, or other features and to display relevant marketing to you.

We use IP addresses to analyse trends, administer our Site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. Additionally, for systems administration, detecting usage patterns and troubleshooting purposes, our web servers automatically log standard access information including browser type, access times/open mail, URL requested, and referral URL.

When we use tracking information to determine which areas of our Site users like and don't like based on traffic to those areas. We track search terms entered in Search function as one of many measures of what interests our users.

MyNaturalMarket creates aggregate reports on user demographics and traffic patterns for advertisers, sponsors and partners. This allows our advertisers to advertise more effectively, and allows our users to receive advertisements that are pertinent to their needs.

USAGE TRACKING

MyNaturalMarket tracks user traffic patterns throughout our Site. However, we do not correlate this information with data about individual users. MyNaturalMarket does break down overall usage statistics according to a users domain name, browser type, and MIME type by reading this information from the browser string (information contained in every users browser).

MyNaturalMarket sometimes tracks and catalogs the search terms that users enter in our Search function. We use tracking information to determine which areas of our Site users like and don't like based on traffic to those areas.

SHARING OF THE INFORMATION

MyNaturalMarket uses the above-described information to tailor our content to you and help our advertisers and partners better understand our audience demographics. We may provide your information to our affiliated companies and trusted third parties in the conduct of our business. Some of these third parties handle our credit card processing, shipping, data management, email distributions, market research, information analysis and promotions management.

Sometimes we are required by law to share your information. Upon a governmental request, in response to a court order, when required by law, to enforce our policies, or to protect our or others' rights, property or safety are all situations in which we may share your information. We may share information to prevent illegal use of our products and services or violations of the Terms of Use, or to defend ourselves against third-party claims. We may also share information with companies assisting in fraud protection or investigation.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to the Site and other sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

Finally, your information may be transferred to a third party as a part of our business assets in a sale of a part or all of MyNaturalMarket. If this should happen, notice will be provided by posting to the Site or other form of communication.

On September 29th, WFM Online Inc. purchased this website from My Natural Market, Inc. (the "Former MNM"). In order to ensure a smooth transition for our customers, including fulfilling your order without having you re-enter account information, we may sometimes share your email address with MNM and ask them to provide us with information related to your account and prior purchases via this website. 

SECURITY

Our data networks are protected by industry standard firewall and password protection systems. Our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary and only authorized individuals have access to the information provided by our customers. However, like other companies, we cannot guarantee the safety and security of your information.

MODIFYING OR DELETING YOUR INFORMATION

You can modify or delete your profile, through your account. Your information previously posted may still be publicly viewable and we may keep information and content in our backup files and archives.

COMMUNICA TION/UNSUBSCRIBE/OPT-OUT

Regardless of the settings you select, we may send you service-related communications. To unsubscribe and stop receiving messages, please change your settings or follow the instructions in the email, text message, notification or other message type. If you have unsubscribed from any our communications, due to production schedules, you may receive communications already in production.

INTERNATIONAL USERS

Our digital operations are conducted, in whole or in part, in the United States. Regardless of where you live, you consent to have your personal data transferred, processed and stored in the United States, and allow us to use and collect your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

TERMS OF USE

Your use of our products and services, and any disputes arising from them, is subject to this Privacy Policy as well as our [Terms of Use](https://www.mynaturalmarket.com/terms.html). Please carefully read our [Terms of Use](https://www.mynaturalmarket.com/terms.html) which explains other terms governing the use of Site, as well as our products and services.

For questions or concerns, please contact MyNaturalMarket at: cs@mynaturalmarket.com or MyNaturalMarket Privacy, 313 W 12800 S Ste 301, Draper UT 84020
